(Leonard:)I know, and I'm
proud of you,
(Leonard:)but that doesn't mean I
can't do something nice.
(Howard:)Like this.
(Penny:)Okay, I don't want this
to turn into a fight.
(Leonard:)I don't, either.
Great.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Can you pass the salt, please?
Sure.
(Leonard:)In my mind, that broke
the tension with comedy
(Leonard:)and led to sex.
(clears throat)
(Raj:)Hey, Sheldon, you busy?
(Sheldon:)I'm always busy.
(Sheldon:)This mind is capable
of advanced multitasking.
(Sheldon:)You know, currently,
(Sheldon:)I'm attempting to solve
(Sheldon:)the Penrose conjecture,
(Sheldon:)I'm composing
my Nobel acceptance speech
(Sheldon:)for when I've solved
the Penrose conjecture,
(Sheldon:)and I'm wondering
how mermaids have babies.
(Raj:)Don't they lay eggs on a rock?
(Sheldon:)Now I've got room
for another thing.
(Sheldon:)What do you want?